A Guide to the Charles Veatch Collection
George Mason University Libraries
- The Charles Veatch Collection
  - Business Report - Richmond Highway Corridor/Southeast Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1995, Folder 29 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report - Tysons Corner Area Report By the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1995, Folder 30 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report - Annandale - Bailey's Crossroads - Seven Corners Area Market Report by the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1994, Folder 31 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report - Reston - Herndon - Area Market Report by the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1994, Folder 32 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report - Springfield - Interstate 95 Corridor Area Market Report by the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1994, Folder 33 (Box Box 14)
  - Western Fairfax Area Market Report by the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1994, Folder 34 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County, Virginia Informative Folder, Folder 35 (Box Box 14)
  - A Proposal for an Innovative, Multimodal Position, Phased Transit System for Northern Virginia Dulles Transportation Corridor - WATF Jan. 1998, Folder 36 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax Plan Monitoring - State of the Plan: An Evaluation of Comprehensive Plan Activities between 1990-95 With an Assessments of Impacts Through 2010, Folder 37 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County Characteristics - 1996 Brochure, Folder 38 (Box Box 14)
  - The Education Foundation - Memorandum Containing A Draft of the "Desirable Criteria for the Superintendent Selection" 6/20/97, Folder 39 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County Virginia - Memorandum Regarding Handouts from the February 1998 EAC Meetings, Folder 40 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County Economic Advisory Committee - Economic Strategic Plan - April 1995, Folder 41 (Box Box 14)
  - Veach's Itinerary for a Trip to San Francisco In 1998, Folder 42 (Box Box 14)
  - Resolving Development Disputes - A Worship On Negotiation and Joint Problem - Solving Tools For Those Concerned About Land Development Disputes In Northern Virginia, Oct 13, 1990, Folder 43 (Box Box 14)
  - The Charles A. Veatch Company - Commercial Real Estate Brokers and Consultants - Information Packet, Folder 44 (Box Box 14)
  - The Reston Center for Industry and Government Declarations, Folder 45 (Box Box 14)
  - OCP Presentation Economic Advisory Commission Meeting June 18, 1997, Folder 46 (Box Box 14)